{"data":{"site":{"pathPrefix":"/restaurant-inspections"},"postgres":{"establishment":[{"establishmentid":"4339","name":"Comerica Park- Mobile Venues","address":"2100 Woodward Ave","zipcode":"48201","owner":"Detroit Sportservice Inc","licenseNumber":"069244","licenseType":"Fixed Establishment","establishmentType":"Food Service Establishment","establishmentStatus":"Open","riskCategory":null,"reviewFrequencyDays":"365.0","coords":"-83.04880,42.33918","geojson":{"id":"4339","type":"Feature","geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[-83.04879849,42.339180497]},"properties":{"name":"Comerica Park- Mobile Venues","owner":"Detroit Sportservice Inc","address":"2100 Woodward Ave","zipcode":"48201","license_type":"Fixed Establishment","risk_category":null,"license_number":"069244","establishmentid":"4339","establishment_type":"Food Service Establishment","establishment_status":"Open","review_frequency_days":"365.0","most_recent_license_date":"4/25/2017"}},"nearbyList":[{"establishmentid":"3475","name":"Chelis Chili Bar","address":"47 E Adams Ave","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"2048","name":"Elwood Bar & Grill","address":"300 E Adams","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"355","name":"Detroit Athletic Club","address":"241 Madison Ave","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"1265","name":"Central Methodist Church","address":"23 E Adams","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"322","name":"Twentieth Century Club, (Gem Theatre)","address":"333 Madison","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"2637","name":"The Fillmore Detroit (State Bar/Theatre)","address":"2101-2115 Woodward Ste 971","zipcode":"48201"},{"establishmentid":"1680","name":"Michigan Opera Theater","address":"1526 Broadway St","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"5189","name":"Dilla's Delight's LLC","address":"242 John R","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"3706","name":"Angelina Italian Bistro","address":"1565 Broadway","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"4694","name":"Madison Building ","address":"1555 Broadway","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"5152","name":"Ashe Supply Co.","address":"1555 Broadway St","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"5132","name":"Vertical Detroit","address":"1538 Centre St","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"296","name":"Da Edoardo Foxtown Grille","address":"2203 Woodward Ave","zipcode":"48201"},{"establishmentid":"5248","name":"234 Winder St. Inn Community Center","address":"2458 Brush St","zipcode":"48201"},{"establishmentid":"4262","name":"Ford Field- Bar Portables","address":"2000 Brush St","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"4884","name":"Ford Field- Detroit Lions Tunnel Club","address":"2000 Brush St","zipcode":"48201"},{"establishmentid":"4260","name":"Ford Field- Employee Lounge","address":"2000 Brush St","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"51622506","name":"Ford Field- South Club (Hall of Legends)","address":"2000 Brush St","zipcode":"48201"},{"establishmentid":"51622504","name":"Ford Field- Terrace Club","address":"2000 Brush St","zipcode":"48201"},{"establishmentid":"4255","name":"Ford Field- Levy Rest. (Main Kitchen)","address":"2000 Brush St","zipcode":"48226"}],"inspectionsByEstablishmentidList":[{"inspectionid":"42339","inspectionDate":"2018-05-16T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"3-501.16","violationDescription":"Except during preparation, cooking, or cooling, or when time is used as the public health control POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD) shall be maintained:\r\n(A)  135ºF or above, except that roasts properly cooked and cooled may be held              at a temperature of 130ºF; or (P)\r\n(B)   At 41ºF or less (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Hot food item(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored below 135 degrees F","subProblem":"","location":"PORTABLE","subLocation":"At the Hot holding temperatures","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-05-16T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Store above 135 degrees F."},{"violationCode":"4-501.114","violationDescription":"A chemical SANITIZER used in a SANITIZING solution for a manual or\r\nmechanical operation shall meet these limits or as otherwise approved: (P)\r\n\tChlorine        ppm           pH<10             pH<8\r\n\t\t      25              120 F              120 F\r\n\t\t      50              100 F              75 F\r\n\t\t     100              55 F               55 F\r\n                 Iodine           a concentration of between 12.5 and 25 ppm and minimum temp of 75 F and pH of 5 or less or meets manufacturer's specifications. (P)\r\n\r\n                Quats            minimum temperature of 75 F, hardness of 500 ppm or less and meet manufacturers use directions. (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Quaternary ammonia solution","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Below 100 ppm","subProblem":"","location":"PORTABLE","subLocation":"At the Sanitizer bucket","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-05-16T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide correct concentration as stated above."},{"violationCode":"3-501.16","violationDescription":"Except during preparation, cooking, or cooling, or when time is used as the public health control POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD) shall be maintained:\r\n(A)  135ºF or above, except that roasts properly cooked and cooled may be held              at a temperature of 130ºF; or (P)\r\n(B)   At 41ºF or less (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Cold food item(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored above 41 degrees F","subProblem":"","location":"PORTABLE","subLocation":"At the COLD HOLDING TEMPERATURES","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-05-16T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Discard"},{"violationCode":"5-202.12","violationDescription":"(A) A handwashing sink shall be equipped to provide water at a temperature of at least 38°C (100°F) through a mixing valve or combination faucet. (Pf)  \r\n(B) A steam mixing valve may not be used at a handwashing sink.  \r\n(C) A self-closing, slow-closing, or metering faucet shall provide a flow of water for at least 15 seconds without the need to reactivate the faucet.   \r\n(D) An automatic handwashing facility shall be installed in accordance with manufacturer's instructions.\r\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Handwashing facility","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Lack of hot water","subProblem":"","location":"PORTABLE","subLocation":"At the HOT WATER","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-05-16T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide hot water."},{"violationCode":"6-301.11","violationDescription":"Each HANDWASHING SINK or group of 2 adjacent HANDWASHING SINKS shall be provided with a supply of hand cleaning liquid, powder, or bar soap. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Soap","subItem":"at handsink","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"At hand sink","location":"HANDSINK(S)","subLocation":"At the Handwashing soap","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-05-16T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide"}]},{"inspectionid":"38733","inspectionDate":"2017-05-18T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"3-501.16","violationDescription":"Except during preparation, cooking, or cooling, or when time is used as the public health control POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD) shall be maintained:\r\n(A)  135ºF or above, except that roasts properly cooked and cooled may be held              at a temperature of 130ºF; or (P)\r\n(B)   At 41ºF or less (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Cold food item(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored above 41 degrees F","subProblem":"","location":"PORTABLE","subLocation":"At the COLD HOLDING TEMPERATURES","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-05-18T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Discard"},{"violationCode":"4-501.114","violationDescription":"A chemical SANITIZER used in a SANITIZING solution for a manual or\r\nmechanical operation shall meet these limits or as otherwise approved: (P)\r\n\tChlorine        ppm           pH<10             pH<8\r\n\t\t      25              120 F              120 F\r\n\t\t      50              100 F              75 F\r\n\t\t     100              55 F               55 F\r\n                 Iodine           a concentration of between 12.5 and 25 ppm and minimum temp of 75 F and pH of 5 or less or meets manufacturer's specifications. (P)\r\n\r\n                Quats            minimum temperature of 75 F, hardness of 500 ppm or less and meet manufacturers use directions. (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Quaternary ammonia solution","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Below 100 ppm","subProblem":"","location":"PORTABLE","subLocation":"At the Sanitizer bucket","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-05-18T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide correct concentration as stated above."},{"violationCode":"5-104.12","violationDescription":"Water meeting the requirements shall be made available for a mobile facility, for a TEMPORARY FOOD ESTABLISHMENT without a permanent water supply, and for a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT with a temporary interruption of its water supply through an approved method. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":null,"subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not approved for use","subProblem":"","location":"PORTABLE","subLocation":"At the Handsink","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-05-18T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Obtain approval for use."},{"violationCode":"5-205.11","violationDescription":"(A) A HANDWASHING SINK shall be maintained so that it is accessible at all times for EMPLOYEE use and used for no other purpose. (Pf)\r\n(B)  An automatic handwashing facility shall be used in accordance with manufacturer's instructions. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Handwashing sink(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not easily accessible","subProblem":"Items stored In","location":"PORTABLE","subLocation":"At the Handsink","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-05-18T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Remove items from handsink.  Do not store items at handsink."},{"violationCode":"6-301.12","violationDescription":"Each HANDWASHING SINK or group of adjacent HANDWASHING SINKS shall be provided with:\r\n(A) Individual, disposable towels; (Pf)\r\n(B) A continuous towel system that supplies the user with a clean towel;(Pf) or \r\n(C) A heated-air hand drying device.(Pf)\r\n(D) A hand drying device that employs an air-knife system that delivers high velocity pressurized air at ambient temperatures.(Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Sanitary hand drying provisions","subItem":"disposable, paper towels","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"PORTABLE","subLocation":"At the Hand-drying towels","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-05-18T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide as required"},{"violationCode":"7-102.11","violationDescription":"Working containers used for storing POISONOUS OR TOXIC MATERIALS such as cleaners and SANITIZERS taken from bulk supplies shall be clearly and individually identified with the common name of the material. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Working containers-toxics","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not labeled as to content","subProblem":"","location":"PORTABLE","subLocation":"At the Chemicals","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-05-18T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Label containers with common name."}]},{"inspectionid":"36440","inspectionDate":"2016-08-31T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[]}]}]}},"pageContext":{"eid":"4339"}}